# **Ronen Lapushner**

Cellphone: +972-50-2669606 Email: ronenk17@gmail.com Portfolio: ronen25.github.io

I am a highly motivated C/C++ developer, with more than 6 years of vast, proven experience with many environments. Currently looking for student/part-time positions, so that I could contribute and study at the same time.

## **Professional Skills**

## Languages/Platforms

- C (C99/11)
- C++ (03, 14+)
- Python 3
- Java
- QML (Qt 5+)
- Rust
- Linux/Unix, Windows

#### Backend

- Cross-platform development with native tools
- Multithreding
- Multiprocessing
- POSIX API
- Win32 API

#### **GUI** Frameworks

- Qt 5+
- Swing
- wxWidgets (3.x)
- Tk
- PyQt / qt-python
- dear ImGui

### Software

- GCC Toolchains
- Valgrind
- LLVM Utilities
- Doxygen
- QMake/CMake/ Autotools

# **Experience**

## **Cyren** *Software Engineer / Tech Lead (Full Time)*

September 2016 – January 2019

- Development and maintenance of a cross-platform (Windows, \*nix, MacOS), cross-architecture, full-stack application.
- Using LLVM's sanitizers to standardize and improve code quality.
- AGILE development and tight integration of customer relations.
- Granular per-architecture optimization and/or development of the product.
- Rewriting old code with C++14-compliant code.
- Reverse engineering and Documentation of previously undocumented systems.

## Israeli Air Force (IAF) – Ofek Unit Programmer

December 2013 – August 2016

- Honorable discharge with very high commendations.
- Development of highly-classified logistic and automation systems.
- Conceptualization, design and implementation of advanced communications and data systems.
- Full Stack End-to-End and prototyping using different development platforms.

## **Education**

# **Open University of Israel**

July 2018 - Present

• B.Sc. in Computer Science, 85 average. Projected graduation: October 2022.

### **BASMACH** Shalishut Base, Ramat-Gan, Israel

September – December 2013

• NTMM (*Nat-Mam*) Course for DevOps engineers, graduated with excellence.

# Tchernichovski High School Netanya, Israel

September 2007 – June 2013

• Complete Matriculation diploma with 5 units in Computer Science and Physics.

# **Spoken Languages**

**Hebrew:** Native language **English:** Native level

Recommendations/grade sheets will be forwarded upon request.